Daniel Gawne

Full Stack Developer

danielgawne@gmail.com dgawne.com

386-848-9757

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/dgwne/

GitHub: https://github.com/dgwn

Skills

I am experienced in Python, Javascript, AWS, HTML, CSS/Sass, ReactJS, Flask, Django, Git, NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, postgreSQL, Typescript, Linux Server Admin, Docker, CI/CD, Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, and XD. I am a self-taught programmer which demonstrates my dedication to continued and self-directed learning.

Experience

University of Central Florida, Center for Distributed Learning / Applications Programmer II

MARCH 2023 - PRESENT, Orlando, FL

Design code, test, debug, integrate, modify, and document applications in support of digital learning. Assist with the implementation of UX designs, database, and back-end development. Assist with analysis and troubleshooting of issues with features in applications, websites, or utility tools. Provide end-user support in collaboration with senior developers, support staff, via faculty development venues, and co-authoring of technical documents. Research and implement improvements to applications/technologies based on industry standards in digital learning.

Raterlabs, Inc. / Senior Internet Analyst

JUNE 2017 - PRESENT, Remote

Conduct research, evaluation and feedback on search engine results by, but not limited to: measuring the relevance and usefulness of web pages in correlation to predefined queries, by providing comparative analysis of sets of search engine results and various other techniques. Evaluate and improve search engine results for some of the world's largest internet search engine companies. Consistently meets high quality standards on monthly reviews and performs in the top 10% of employees.

Fleet Farming / Digital Media/Marketing Intern

JAN 2018 - MAY 2018, Orlando, FL

Developed targeted Facebook ad campaigns for selected demographics, wrote original ad copy, managed Facebook and Instagram feeds, calculated effectiveness of ad spending on sales and brand awareness, monitored Google Analytics for our website, monitored and selected keywords using Google AdWords, drafted and designed promotional materials for both print and web (e.g. fliers, calendar, infographics, and stickers), and developed action plans for future interns in the Media/Marketing department.

Education

University of Helsinki/ Computer Science

2022 - Present

University of Central Florida/ Philosophy B.A. (Sociology Minor)

2012 - 2017, Orlando, FL